<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kipi_plugins</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KIPI Plugins</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Connectors KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connectors KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Moduly KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KIPI πρόσθετα</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KIPI Plugins</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Complementos KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KIPI pluginad</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KIPI pluginak</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KIPI-liitännäiset</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Modules externes KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Complementos de KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Plugins de Kipi</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Estensioni KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KIPI 플러그인</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KIPI-plug-ins</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KIPI-tillegg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">'Plugins' do KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Plugins KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Подключаемые модули KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Zásuvné moduly KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv"> KIPI-insticksprogram</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Додатки KIPI</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKIPI Pluginsxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KIPI 外掛程式</name>
  <summary>Plugins for KDE applications to export images</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Connectors per a les aplicacions KDE per exportar imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connectors per a les aplicacions KDE per exportar imatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Πρόσθετα για KDE εφαρμογές εξαγωγής εικόνων</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Plugins for KDE applications to export images</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Complementos para exportar imágenes en aplicaciones de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">KDE rakenduste pluginad piltide eksportimiseks</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">KDE aplikazioek irudiak esportatu ditzaten pluginak</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Kuvien viemisen liitännäiset KDE-sovelluksille</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Modules externes d'exportation d'images pour les applications KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Complementos para que as aplicacións de KDE exporten imaxes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Plugins per applicationes de KDE de exportar images</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Estensioni per far esportare le immagini alle applicazioni di KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE 프로그램에서 그림을 내보내는 플러그인</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Plug-ins voor KDE toepassingen om afbeeldingen te exporteren</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">'Plugins' para as aplicações do KDE exportarem imagens</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Plugins de exportação de imagens para aplicativos do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Подключаемые модули экспорта изображений для приложений KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Insticksprogram för KDE-program för att exportera bilder</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Додатки до програм KDE для експортування зображень</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxPlugins for KDE applications to export imagesxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">適用於 KDE 應用程式用來匯出影像的外掛程式</summary>
  <description>
    <p>These plugins export image to various services such as Mediawiki or Facebook or a local album.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquests connectors exporten imatge a diversos serveis com el Mediawiki, el Facebook o un àlbum local.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aquests connectors exporten imatge a diversos serveis com el Mediawiki, el Facebook o un àlbum local.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Αυτά τα πρόσθετα εξάγουν εικόνες σε διάφορες υπηρεσίες όπως το Mediawiki ή το Facebook ή ένα τοπικό άλμπουμ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">These plugins export image to various services such as Mediawiki or Facebook or a local album.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Estos complementos exportan imágenes a diversos servicios, como Mediawiki o Facebook, o a un álbum local.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Need pluginad võimaldavad eksportida pilte paljudesse teenustesse, nagu näiteks Mediawiki või Facebook või kas või kohalik album.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Plugin hauek irudiak hainbat zerbitzutara esportatzen dituzte, Mediawiki-ra, Facebook-era edo album lokaletara esaterako.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Nämä liitännäiset vievät kuvia eri palveluihin kuten MediaWikiin, Facebookiin tai paikalliseen albumiin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ces modules externes exportent les images vers différents services comme Mediawiki, Facebook ou un album local.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Estes complementos exportan imaxes a varios servizos, como Mediawiki ou Facebook, ou un álbum local.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Queste estensioni esportano immagini su molti servizi, come Mediawiki o Facebook, oppure un album locale.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 플러그인은 미디어위키, Facebook, 로컬 앨범 등 다양한 서비스로 그림을 내보냅니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Deze plug-ins exporteren afbeeldingen naar verschillende services zoals Mediawiki of Facebook of een lokaal album.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Estes 'plugins' exportam as imagens para vários serviços, como o Mediawiki, o Facebook ou um álbum local.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Estes plugins exportam as imagens para vários serviços, como o Mediawiki ou Facebook ou um álbum local.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Модули позволяют экспортировать изображения в как различные веб-сервисы, такие как, например, MediaWiki или Facebook, так и в локальные альбомы.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Insticksprogrammen exporterar bilder till diverse tjänster såsom Mediawiki, Facebook eller ett lokalt album.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою цих додатків можна експортувати зображення до різноманітних служб, зокрема Mediawiki та Facebook, або до локального альбому.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThese plugins export image to various services such as Mediawiki or Facebook or a local album.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">這些外掛程式能匯出圖片至各種服務（例如 MediaWiki、Facebook 等）或本機相簿。</p>
    <p>They add export features to Gwenview and Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Afegeixen funcionalitats d'exportació al Gwenview i l'Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Afigen funcionalitats d'exportació al Gwenview i l'Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Προσθέτουν λειτουργίες εξαγωγής σε Gwenview και Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">They add export features to Gwenview and Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Añaden funciones de exportación a Gwenview y a Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Nendega saab lisada rakendustele Gwenview ja Spectacle täiendavaid võimalusi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Esportatzeko eginbideak gehitzen dizkiete Gwenview eta Spectacle-ri.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ne lisäävät vientiominaisuuden Gwenview’hun ja Spectacleen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ils ajoutent des fonctionnalités d'exportation à Gwenview et Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Engaden funcionalidades de exportación a Gwenview e Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Aggiungono funzionalità di esportazione a Gwenview e Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Gwenview 및 Spectacle에 내보내기 기능을 추가합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Ze voegen exportfuncties toe aan Gwenview en Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Eles adicionam as funcionalidades de exportação ao Gwenview e ao Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Eles adicionam as funcionalidades de exportação ao Gwenview e Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Эти модули используются в приложениях Gwenview и Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">De lägger till exportfunktioner i Gwenview och Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Додають можливості з експортування до Gwenview та Spectacle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThey add export features to Gwenview and Spectacle.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">其會對 Gwenview 及 Spectacle 加入匯出功能。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kipiplugins</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kipi-plugins</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default"><caption>KIPI Plugins as used in Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="ca">Connectors KIPI com s'usen al Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connectors KIPI com s'usen al Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="el">KIPI πρόσθετα όπως χρησιμοποιούνται στο Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="en-GB">KIPI Plugins as used in Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="es">Complementos KIPI en Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="et">KIPI pluginate kasutamine Gwenview's.</caption><caption xml:lang="eu">KIPI pluginak Gwenview-n erabili bezala.</caption><caption xml:lang="fi">KIPI-liitännäiset käytössä Gwenview’ssa.</caption><caption xml:lang="fr">Modules externes de KIPI tels qu'utilisés dans Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="gl">Os complementos de KIPI tal e como se usan en Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="it">Le estensioni di KIPI come usate in Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="ko">Gwenview에서 KIPI 플러그인을 사용하는 방법입니다.</caption><caption xml:lang="nl">KIPI-plug-ins zoals gebruikt in Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="pt">Os 'Plugins' do KIPI usados no Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Os plugins KIPI usados no Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="ru">Использование модулей KIPI в Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="sv"> KIPI-insticksprogram som de används i Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="uk">Додатки KIPI працюють у Gwenview.</caption><caption xml:lang="x-test">xxKIPI Plugins as used in Gwenview.xx</caption><caption xml:lang="zh-TW">當用在 Gwenview 時的 KIPI 外掛程式。</caption>
​      <image type="source" width="496" height="488">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kipi-plugins/kipi-plugins.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <extends>org.kde.gwenview.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.spectacle.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.kphotoalbum</extends>
  <categories>
    <category>Graphics</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">kipi</icon>
</component>
